b'No president should be scared of the truth.'
b'The real problem: mass surveillance &amp; deep state trying to subordinate the elected government.'
b'Why is T_D not claiming a part of <SR>/r/place</SR>??'
b'?'
b"Let's cover the communist flag at the left side in the color of guac."
b'Instructions for those that are unaware: Go to <SR>r/place</SR>, scroll around until you find the <GPE>US</GPE> flag, zoom in.'
b'Click on a red, white, or blue tile and put it in the appropriate spot, click again to place it.'
b'The flag is still in good enough condition that you can follow the existing pattern.'
b"It took me way too long to get over there because I didn't feel like looking into it and trying to figure it out."
b'It is not difficult and while it may seem stupid, we should take any opportunity to show off our numbers.'
b'<GPE>MAGA</GPE>'
b'DO IT!'
b'<SR>/r/place</SR> lets you see who is defacing your commie <PRODUCT>Anti-FA</PRODUCT> etchings.'
b'(Yeah, the pink was me.'
b"Pink for the <PERSON>Pinko</PERSON>'s)"
b"'Pedes, seriously enough with the irrelevant <SR>r/place</SR> crap!"
b'Let the commis and antifa have their little star and sickle on some imaginary canvas.'
b'We have this picture in real life!'
b"<PERSON>Ann Coulter</PERSON> on Twitter: <ORG>Airports &</ORG>amp; nuclear power stations on terror alert as govt officials warn of 'credible' cyber threat."
b'#Diversity'
b'<SR>r/place</SR> SAVE PEPE'
b'Save the Flag!'
b'Anyone want to build a WALL on <SR>r/place</SR>?'
b'Looks like our <CARDINAL>5.4 million</CARDINAL> reinforcements have arrived!'
b"Don't let up on the cucks, 'pedes!"
b'I am calling for reinforcements, we need help rebuilding our beautiful flag!'
b'!'
b"How does it feel that you racist, bigoted kike worshippers didn't get a spot in <SR>/r/place</SR>?"
b'Quote from <PERSON>John Jay</PERSON>, Founding Father and first Chief Justice.'
b'A nation cannot be based on multiculturalism.'
b'They keep misspelling <PERSON>N. R. A.</PERSON> on this <SR>r/place</SR> (look under our glorious flag).'
b'Can you guys help us out?'
b'place: draw a crescent moon on swedish flag'
b'PROJECT BLACK - WE NEED HELP FROM EACH AND EVERY PEDE ON HERE.'
b'JavaScript to Help us <GPE>Build</GPE> the <GPE>MAGA</GPE> flag in <SR>r/place</SR>'
b'Tin Foil Hat: What do you all think are the chances this bombing in <GPE>Russia</GPE> is a false flag?'
b'Put Some Trump in <SR>/r/Place</SR> !'
b'We got a flag going; <CARDINAL>6 million</CARDINAL> of us couple easily get a pepe or <GPE>MAGA</GPE> in there!'
b'DEFEND THE <ORG>FLAG</ORG> (<SR>/r/place</SR>)'
b'People are not going to let us put "The_Donald" on <SR>/r/Place</SR> so let\'s at least defend the flag and "e pluribus unum" motto!'
b'The flag and motto is from (<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>467</CARDINAL>) to (<CARDINAL>571</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>546</CARDINAL>)'
b'The <NORP>American</NORP> flag in <SR>/r/place</SR> is getting destroyed.'
b"Come <CARDINAL>one</CARDINAL> <SR>/r/The_Donald</SR> let's fix it"
b'<ORG>Old Glory</ORG> will not fade in the face of <DATE>Degeneracy</DATE>!'
b'WE MUST BE VIGILANT IN /PLACE'
b'Why is there no Pepe on <SR>r/place</SR>?'
b'From what I can see <SR>r/place</SR> needs a little <GPE>MAGA</GPE> enrichment'
b'reds are attempting to take over snek on <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'T_D has a special salute for <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'Will you help draw <ORG>Pepe</ORG> in <SR>/r/place</SR> with this bot?'
b'for those who are doing that place thing...some punk put an <ORG>NPR</ORG> logo under the flag.'
b"not cool, but it looks like it's being destroyed pretty quick"
b'<ORG>Reddit</ORG> admins quickly try to hide their subscriber leak with impressions, but the code still says subscribers.'
b'<SR>/r/place</SR> needs you!'
b'<PERCENT>50%</PERCENT> Upvoted??'
b'We need to fight to keep the flag up!'
b'<ORG>CBS News</ORG> now reporting <CARDINAL>15,000</CARDINAL> <NORP>Russian</NORP> bots spreading fake news and conspiracy theories swung <ORG>the White House</ORG> to President <PERSON>Trump</PERSON>.'
b'Wait until they hear about what the other <CARDINAL>300,000</CARDINAL> of us did.'
b'I think we should drop the flag/place fucking around, but here is something cool.'
b'<ORG>Gif</ORG> of the board over there, animated heatmap style.'
b'Check out just before the end of the gif, in the middle :)'
b'Just NOW ON FOX AND FRIENDS , the MSM SPENT EXACTLY ZERO MINUTES COVERING THE POTUS UNMASKING STORY'
b'The single biggest story of our<GPE>\nLifetimes</GPE> .'
b'Remember this pedes .'
b'Remember.'
b'THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERS RIGHT NOW , IS GETTING THE EVELYN FARKAS STORY EVERY FUCKING WHERE .'
b'Fuck this <SR>r/place</SR> shit and get to work people !!'
b'THINGS ARE  GETTING VERY TENSE IN <GPE>WASHINGTON</GPE> ...'
b'President <PERSON>Trump</PERSON>: "<GPE>CALIFORNIA</GPE> IS A <ORG>MAJOR</ORG> DISASTER" <GPE>Cuckafornia</GPE> BTFO'
b"LET'S TAKE THIS BEAUTIFUL <ORG>FLAG</ORG> TO THE <ORG>NEXT</ORG> LEVEL!"
b'commies are still trying to grief it, lets show them what <ORG>FREEDOM</ORG> tastes like!'
b"<ORG>MFW</ORG> all my liberal friends don't know I took the red pill and am slowly working them"
b"Here's my next classic art inspired meme."
b'I call it "A <DATE>Sunday</DATE> <TIME>Afternoon</TIME> on <LOC>the Island Maga</LOC> (and <WORK_OF_ART>a Side of Beef</WORK_OF_ART>)".'
b'WE NEED YOUR HELP!'
b'HELP <GPE>US</GPE> ON <SR>/R/PLACE</SR>'
b'Help make a big <NORP>AMERICAN</NORP> flag here!'
b"lnc: please go to sleep, it's late."
b"Hey everyone, it's <TIME>another late night</TIME> in the Jeb!"
b'Presidency here on <DATE>April 1st</DATE>.'
b"I'm /u/<ORG>DatabaseCentral</ORG> and *unfortunately* I'm awake with all of you other <PRODUCT>Jeb</PRODUCT>!"
b'supporters <DATE>today</DATE>.'
b"I'll probably be heading out soon, not really able to stick around."
b"I need some sleep, and I'd suggest you get some too."
b'This is an important announcement, honestly.'
b"We has stripped caps from post titles because it's been too high energy for a subreddit like ours."
b"Please, if you're in the mood <DATE>today</DATE> (I know some of us aren't), feel free to clap on the side, or visit our new presidential brother subreddit on the sidebar, <SR>/r/The_Guacbowl</SR>."
b'This is a place where Jeb!'
b'supporters can get some rest from some insane high energy that we see throughout <DATE>the day</DATE>.'
b"If you're struggling to sleep, here's a couple videos I still love from <DATE>the past couple years</DATE>:\n\n[I've Delivered](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hkG3J7Wp0Qs) (and yes he has!"
b'Ever since he became president, life has been much better.)'
b'[Talkers vs Leaders](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=<GPE>TnyGJstIB4U</GPE>) (And we know that Jeb!'
b'knows how to lead.)'
b"[Flipping for <ORG>Jeb](https://www.youtube.com</ORG>/watch?v=<GPE>j8cV1es</GPE>-Hf0) (I know there's a lot of hostility in the world <DATE>today</DATE>, I please suggest all of you take after this ad and show the left that it's okay to flip to Jeb!)"
b"**Alright, Now it's time to the normal LNC <PERSON>Audio Books</PERSON>:**\n\n* [<DATE>1984</DATE> by <PERSON>George Orwell</PERSON> (full audiobook)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=<TIME>auwRj4Yru-E)</TIME>\n\n* [<ORG>Animal Farm</ORG> by <PERSON>George Orwell</PERSON> (full audiobook)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gl4REOWdJSE)\n\n* [<PERSON>Green Eggs</PERSON> and Ham by Dr. <PERSON>Seuss</PERSON> (full audiobook)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vnxHL4gwuqU)\n\n* [<WORK_OF_ART>The Art of the Deal by</WORK_OF_ART> <PERSON>Donald Trump</PERSON> (full audiobook)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=<GPE>T9KoFwHDJ3c</GPE>)"
b'<PERSON>Donald J. Trump</PERSON>: Did <PERSON>Hillary Clinton</PERSON> ever apologize for receiving the answers to the debate?'
b'Just asking!'
b'The void is trying to reestablish itself!'
b'Defend the flag at <SR>r/place</SR>!'
b'Obama may have used <GPE>Tahiti</GPE> as a jumping off place to flee into obscurity.'
b'If <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> has fled <GPE>Tahiti</GPE>, look for other <ORG>Swamp</ORG> creatures to also start disappearing.'
b'I see you guys on <SR>/r/place</SR> ;)'
b'dat <ORG>Pepe</ORG> and "<PERSON>BILL CLINTON</PERSON> IS A <ORG>RAPIST</ORG>"'
b'WE NEED HELP ON <SR>R/PLACE</SR>'
b'We need to create teams for the <SR>r/The_Donald</SR> sign above the <NORP>American</NORP> Flag on place.'
b'I\'ll concentrate on "e"'
b'Anybody wanna help turn the german flag in the lower left corner on <SR>r/place</SR> into the official flag of the <NORP>Islamic</NORP> Caliphate of <GPE>Germanistan</GPE>?'
b"Title says everything, 'nuff said."
b'Was thinking of something like this:\n\nhttp://shoebat.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/flag_of_germanistan.jpg'
b"Remembering the Fallen 'Pedes of the Memeocaust"
b'I need to ask you patriots a favor (x-post from <SR>/r/Murica</SR>)'
b'Over at <SR>/r/place</SR> all hell is breaking loose.'
b'Our <NORP>American</NORP> flag, while complete is totally disproportionate.'
b"We have like <DATE>25 30</DATE> striped when it's supposed to have <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>."
b"If we don't get out act together out beautiful piece of art, the red white and blue will be overrun."
b'If I could get a everyone who reads this to go over there and place cubes so that the flag is morphed into something more proportionate, it would keep the legacy of <ORG>Old Glory</ORG> like never before.'
b'Arise now!'
b'Champions Of the <GPE>US</GPE>, and Make America Great Again'
b'Help us build the wall on <SR>R/Place</SR>.'
b'see comments for <ORG>Discord</ORG> link.'
b'Join us!'
b'What do we know about <PERSON>Mark Wahlberg</PERSON>?'
b"I'm digging this shirt though."
b'<ORG>MFW</ORG> I see terrorist organization antifa claim "dictator <PERSON>Trump</PERSON> is working for <GPE>Russia</GPE>" while they are holding up a <GPE>Soviet Union</GPE> flag.'
b"What's this shit?"
b"Can't comment, can't report it... Fuck you Insta!"
b"<ORG>Reddit</ORG>'s <SR>r/Place</SR> openly advocates for violence."
b"I don't think <ORG>Reddit</ORG>'s advertisers would be happen with this."
b'Imagine if this said "Bash the <NORP>Muslim</NORP>" instead.'
b'Take over the commie corner on <SR>r/place</SR>!'
b'Why I became a conservative overnight'
b'I was raised STRONGLY liberal in an upper middle class white family of <CARDINAL>four</CARDINAL>.'
b'To sum up my families political beliefs; guns are bad and if you own one, your toddler will find a way to shoot themselves with it no matter how well you lock it up, obama was jesus reincarnated, christians are all evil bible thumpers, and <NORP>republicans</NORP> are all rich white greedy old men who want you to starve to death.'
b'My mom was a stay at home mom and my dad was a software engineer.'
b'As soon as <PERSON>Donald Trump</PERSON> and <PERSON>Hillary Clinton</PERSON> were selected as candidates for this election, my parents panicked.'
b'Like, "if he wins, we\'re going to leave the country and retire as soon as possible" panicked.'
b'I, barely 19 and a full time university student, was not caught up on politics.'
b'I was spoon fed the idea that <ORG>Trump</ORG> would ruin the united states.'
b'I was told that <ORG>Trump</ORG> was a racist, sexist, misogynistic rapist.'
b'<DATE>A week before election day</DATE>, I started doing my own research.'
b'I read <ORG>CNN</ORG>, <ORG>MSNBC</ORG>, <ORG>BBC</ORG> exc, not knowing at the time that these were <ORG>SERIOUSLY</ORG> biased news networks.'
b'I  came to the conclusion that he was an awful human being and when <DATE>election day</DATE> came around, my liberal mother told me to vote (but really, only if it was for hillary).'
b'She parked in front of a government building after we had finished a "girls <NORP>day"lunch</NORP> and refused to budge until I went in and exercised my right to vote.'
b'I was annoyed, but i went in and voted for <PERSON>Hillary</PERSON>.'
b'Fast forward <DATE>a week</DATE>, and I found out my boyfriend had voted for Trump.'
b'I got upset, naievely believing  everything I had been told about <NORP>Trump</NORP>, and kicked my boyfriend out of the house.'
b'Looking back and knowing what I know now, I really regret that.'
b"(we''re still together, thank god he put up with me.)"
b"Time went by, and <ORG>Trump's</ORG> <DATE>inauguration day</DATE> arrived."
b'I had "come to terms" with his election, and had decided to make the best of <DATE>the next four years</DATE> and hoped for his success.'
b"Then, my boyfriend showed me footage of riots that occured in <GPE>Washington DC</GPE> on <ORG>Trump's</ORG> <DATE>inauguration day</DATE>."
b'<ORG>Antifa</ORG> members charged police on bikes, broke windows (ironically of businesses that funded part of <GPE>Hillaries</GPE> campaign), and attacked groups of <NORP>Trump</NORP> supporters.'
b'Grown women fell to the ground and screeched as if they had just witnessed the death of a child.'
b'Black lives matter rioters destroyed some of their own neighborhoods, and a special needs boy was tortured and scalped on facebook livestream simply for supporting <ORG>Trump</ORG> and being white.'
b"I couldn't believe the reaction of the liberal side, just because a <NORP>republican</NORP> man whom they did not agree with was becoming president."
b'I immediately went to research news articles on <ORG>CNN</ORG>, <ORG>MSNBC</ORG>, <ORG>BBC</ORG> exc for more information, and to my dismay, none of the riots or violence had been covered.'
b'Just page after page of "haha look how dead it is in the whitehouse during <ORG>Trump\'s</ORG> inauguration".'
b'I was appauled.'
b'It became apparent to me that  my "reliable" news sorces had a serious agenda.'
b'I went to my mother and told her of the riots and violence, and she called me a liar.'
b'She told me I had found "fake news", even though the events were recorded live streamed over various social media sites.'
b'Because it was not being covered on the staple news networks of my household, it simply "wasn\'t happening".'
b'I was later told that "even if there were riots and violence against trump supporters, violence is necessary for change.'
b'That\'s how the <NORP>american</NORP> people abolished slavery."'
b'That hit me pretty hard.'
b'My mom, who I love and respect, had compared what was supposed to be a peaceful transition of power to the horrors of slavery.'
b'I asked her if she would still agree with the violence if it took place in our middle class neighborhood.'
b'She told me "we don\'t live in a poor community, it wouldn\'t happen to us."'
b'That really opened my eyes to everything.'
b'She agreed with the rioting and wanted it to occur, but did not want it to occur in OUR neighborhood.'
b'She was not willing to feel the effects of what she pictured as "a solution to <PERSON>Donald Trump</PERSON>".'
b"I attend <ORG>Texas Woman's University</ORG> in which <PERCENT>50%</PERCENT> of the campus demographic are <ORG>POC</ORG>."
b'After the election, professors took up <TIME>the first 20 minutes</TIME> of nearly every lecture to rant about how racist, misogynistic, and sexist our new president was.'
b'I had a math professor assume every mexican in the room was illegal and attempted to comfort them, stating "he\'s not going to boot you out.'
b"He can't."
b'He can\'t catch everybody" (which, to anyone with a brain, was racist).'
b'I overheard classmates openly wish death upon the president of <GPE>the United States</GPE>.'
b'I was disgusted.'
b'<ORG>Classrooms</ORG> began to appear segregated, with many <ORG>POC</ORG> refusing to sit next to white girls.'
b'The few conservative girls that I knew in my classes were visibly annoyed by the the violent talk against <PERSON>Donald Trump</PERSON>, but never spoke up.'
b'My boyfriend was raised in <GPE>El Paso</GPE>, and experienced rampant racism as a minority in his school and neighborhood.'
b'When i mentioned this to a classmate who insisted white people could never experience racism, she told me it wasn\'t racism because he had "white privelege".'
b'That was the final straw for me.'
b'The uncivilized, blatant denial of facts, along with the rise of antifa and the black lives matter movement drove me away from the left wing.'
b'Any dissagreement with a <NORP>democrat</NORP> ended with someone calling me a cis white racist.'
b'<NORP>Democrats</NORP> swore that trump would destroy the country, but while trump was doing what every president has already done, liberals were rioting; destroying neighborhoods, universities, and other public buildings.'
b'Liberal news stations like <ORG>CNN</ORG>, <ORG>MSNBC</ORG>, and <ORG>BBC</ORG> pretended as if the only chaos occurring in <GPE>America</GPE> as a result of the election was because of donald trump.'
b'They called <ORG>Trump a liar</ORG> about the disasterous events in <GPE>Sweden</GPE>, and when they finally had to cover it, they attempted to blame <PERSON>Donald Trump</PERSON> for the attack.'
b'<ORG>MSNBC</ORG> admitted that incidents of rape in <GPE>Sweden</GPE> had increased by <PERCENT>13%</PERCENT>, but it was nothing to worry about because it "wasn\'t any higher than in <DATE>2005</DATE>" (which could also be worded as "incidence of rape in sweden hasn\'t been this bad since <DATE>2005</DATE>").'
b"<ORG>Odd</ORG> coming from a side who swears all men are rapists and that it's a huge epidemic in <NORP>American</NORP> society."
b"To conclude this ridiculously long rant of a post: Trump hasn't done anything to end the country."
b'I am now a firm believer and supporter of <ORG>BLUE</ORG> lives matter, and I strongly believe in the right to own and carry a gun.'
b'I no longer identify with the left wing or feminism.'
b'Honestly if anything, guys have it worse.'
b'Hell, a woman can kill a guys unborn child or take his children during divorce and demand he still pay child support AND alimony.'
b"Guys don't get taken seriously when they try to press charges for rape, guys get the tough blue collar jobs, and so much more."
b"I'll gladly take the <MONEY>$0.70 cents</MONEY> on the dollar that feminists swear is a thing."
b"I know I've got it better."
b"I am now a proud, patriotic conservative and I wouldn't have it any other way."
b'I wish nothing but success for <PERSON>Donald</PERSON> trump.'
b'TLDR: I red pilled myself.'
b"Note:  I don't actually believe in a gender wage gap."
b'I know it\'s been debunked, thus why I said "that feminists swear is a thing" lol'
b'Flags of Europe - 2027'
b'SAVE PEPE https://www.reddit.com<SR>/r/place</SR>#x=530&amp;y=800'
b"<ORG>THE AMERICAN FLAG NEEDS</ORG> YOU'RE HELP AT <SR>R/PLACE</SR>!"
b'Help us Uncuck <SR>/r/place</SR> with a beautiful "Des Vault" logo'
b'DEUS VULT UNDER <ORG>ATTACK</ORG>!!!'
b'MUST PROTECT DEUS VULT!!'
b'!'
b"<SR>r/place</SR> has rejected trump, so lets destroy they're communist flag"
b'Come help build the <GPE>Kekistan</GPE> flag!'
b'(<CARDINAL>269,924</CARDINAL>)'
b'SAVE PEPE https://www.reddit.com<SR>/r/place</SR>#x=530&amp;y=800'
b'IT IS HAPPENING....we have gone from "POTUS has no evidence of ludicrous wire tapping accusation" to arguing over what day it started...\'PEDES we control the narrative now'
b'FIX THE <ORG>FLAG</ORG>!'
b'<SR>r/place</SR> FLAG FIXING SCRIPT!'
b'IDIOT GAY Activists Hold Vile Topless Protest Outside Ivanka Trump\xe2\x80\x99s Home'
b'Concept for an addition to <SR>/r/Place</SR>'
b"Lets show /place who's <ORG>BOSS</ORG>!"
b'!'
b'<PERSON>Tommy Robinson - "</PERSON>We\'ve created a generation of cowards who won\'t stand up to <NORP>Muslims</NORP>" [<GPE>UK</GPE>]'
b'THIS IS THE PLAN <SR>R/PLACE</SR>'
b'A rare <ORG>Pepe</ORG> is forming in the middle of <SR>r/place</SR>, do your part.'
b'WTF!!!'
b'We need (mod) coordinated efforts to take control of <SR>r/place</SR>.'
b"I think we're done with this whole jeb thing."
b"it was fun at <ORDINAL>first</ORDINAL> but now it's just annoying."
b'The Grand Challenge'
b'*Put this:* http://imgur.com/a/0ciZe \n\n*Here:* https://www.reddit.com<SR>/r/place/</SR>\n\nYou have <TIME>24 hours</TIME>!'
b'reinforcements needed!'
b'we at <SR>r/afip</SR> noticed that of all the flags on the <SR>r/place</SR> canvas, the one lacking was our glorious <NORP>american</NORP> flag.'
b'we are now trying to fix this by building a massive flag.'
b'we are being attacked on all fronts by the void and eu freedom hating cucks.'
b'click the link to help!'
b'Why did you all just give up on contributing to <SR>/r/place</SR>?'
b'Yeah...HELL NO to bombing <GPE>Iran</GPE> pre-emptively like we did in <GPE>Iraq</GPE> and <GPE>Libya</GPE>...General of <ORG>USCENTCOM</ORG> wants us to fucking bomb <GPE>IRAN</GPE>!!'
b'!'
b'<ORG>CNN</ORG> the CIAs media arm puts the <NORP>Russian</NORP> bombing in quotes.'
b"'Terror Attack'."
b'Strongly implying it was a false flag.'
b'This level of disrespect is simply preposterous.'
b'Glorious Pede!'
b'<ORG>WaPo</ORG> live links to twitter again!'
b'Fake news never learns...'
b'LGBT'
b"'Pedes, seriously enough with the <SR>r/place</SR> crap."
b'Let the commis and antifa have their little star and sickle on some imaginary canvas.'
b'We have this picture in real life.'
b'GIGANTIC PEPE IN <SR>R/PLACE</SR> WE CAN DO IT CENTIPEDES'
b'Lets show who the king of reddit is'
b'JOIN THE <ORG>THE_DONALD</ORG> <SR>/r/place</SR> <ORG>DISCORD</ORG> SO WE CAN TAKE OVER!!'
b'!'
b'Praise upon those spelling "cuck" on <FAC>the Commie Flag</FAC>.'
b'<GPE>Kekistan</GPE> in <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'(<CARDINAL>420</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>420</CARDINAL>)\nGOGO'
b'We should take over <SR>r/place</SR>.... Would be fun.'
b'Discarded idea.'
b'Shot down too early.'
b'EXTREMELY low energy.'
b'God help us.'
b'yep, this is happening in atlanta'
b'Tweet highlighting the absurdity of college professors gets <CARDINAL>155,000</CARDINAL> <ORG>Likes</ORG>'
b'Calling all proud Kekistani nationals to make a shrine to Kek on <SR>/r/place</SR> at co-ordinates (<CARDINAL>742</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>)'
b'<SR>/r/place</SR>, <CARDINAL>one</CARDINAL> pixel at a time.'
b'You know what to do'
b'Defend the Flag!'
b'Get In Here Pedes!'
b'USE THE <ORG>AFIP</ORG> SCRIPT!'
b"<SR>r/place</SR> is the biggest <ORG>CON</ORG> I've ever seen."
b'It was probably created for the sole purpose of lowering our energy!'
b'<ORG>Fuck /place</ORG>.'
b"Don't fall for it."
b'<SR>r/place</SR> teaches communities the importance of enforcing borders!'
b"I have tried to post photos of the <PERSON>DDoS'd</PERSON> and now hacked <ORG>Rspolitics.com</ORG> site, and none of them will post."
b'Quite the coincidence that they call out <ORG>Reddit</ORG> manipulation and are then attacked and hacked in <TIME>a matter of hours</TIME>.'
b'Check out http://rspolitics.com homepage'
b'OUR <ORG>FLAG</ORG> IS UNDER <ORG>ATTACK</ORG>!'
b'<CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8<CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8<CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8<CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8\xe2\x80\xbc\xef\xb8\x8f\xe2\x80\xbc\xef\xb8\x8fREMINDER TO BE @ <SR>R/PLACE</SR> @.'
b'<ORDINAL>1:00pm</ORDINAL> EST to <GPE>MAGA\xe2\x80\xbc\xef\xb8\x8f\xe2\x80\xbc\xef\xb8\x8f</GPE><CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8<CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8<CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8<CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xba</CARDINAL>\xf0\x9f\x87\xb8'
b'<ORG>Antifa</ORG> wants to commit genocide on the white race starting with the children.'
b'<PERSON>DIVIDE</PERSON> AND CONQUER!'
b'Those who want to support <PERSON>Trumps</PERSON> agenda through news, carry on.'
b'Those who want to support <PERSON>Trumps</PERSON> agenda in a more artful way, feel free to collaborate on <SR>r/place</SR>!'
b'ALERT!'
b'<ORG>THE AMERICAN FLAG ON PLACE</ORG> IS UNDER HEAVY SEIGE.'
b'WE CAN NOT ALLOW THE ONLY <ORG>FULLY</ORG> ERECT AMERICAN FLAG TO BE DESTROYED BY THE COMMIES, SWEDISH CUCKS, AND <PERSON>EU FREEDOM</PERSON> HATING LOSERS.'
b'COME HELP REPAIR AT <CARDINAL>500</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>500</CARDINAL>!!'
b'!'
b'PURGE THE <ORG>SCOURGE</ORG>!'
b'PEDES!'
b'LETS DRAW A <ORG>PEPE</ORG>!'
b'Everybody head over to <SR>r/place</SR> and help draw the meme that triggers all the cucks!'
b'WE NEED <EVENT>A STICKY THREAD FOR</EVENT> <SR>/r/PLACE</SR>.'
b'WE ARE DROWNING IN <ORG>VERMIN</ORG>!'
b"'Pedes, I need your help to get the word out about <LOC>the South Plains Wildfires</LOC>."
b'The farmers and ranchers here who lost so much would love to hear from President <PERSON>Trump</PERSON>.'
b"Like I said in the post title, so many people from the area I live in have lost so much and the liberals in this area are running with the fact that God Emperor hasn't said anything."
b"I'm not worried, but I know that even a line or <CARDINAL>two</CARDINAL> from <PERSON>PT</PERSON> would go a long way for <LOC>the South Plains</LOC>."
b'Here are a few news articles about the fire, some are left leaning, but I wanted to show what some of the libs are saying.'
b"<ORG>South Plains Journal</ORG>, liberal: http://www.hpj.com/opinion/in-wildfire-s-wake-the-president-s-silence-is-deafening/article_37dd790e-c968-51c1-bb89-43266f9a15ac.html\n\n<ORG>The Weather Network</ORG>, neutral: https://www.theweathernetwork.com/us/news/articles/us-weathe<SR>r/fires-ignite-red-flag-warnings-cover-plains-south-florida-oklahoma-texas-new-mexico-kansas-nebraska/80050</SR>\n\n<ORG>NYT</ORG>, liberal paper, neutral article: https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/20/us/burying-their-cattle-ranchers-call-wildfires-our-hurricane-katrina.html\n\n**If we could get this message to President <PERSON>Trump</PERSON> and he would make a statement, it would cement the belief that he truly cares about the growers in this region, thanks 'pedes**"
b'<PERSON>Sorry Erdogan</PERSON>, but Were taking down the <NORP>Turkish</NORP> flag.'
b'did HWNDU get hacked?'
b'just visited to see if <NORP>Shia</NORP> had a new flag up and now its a very bizare looking webpage powered by wordpress.'
b'"<WORK_OF_ART>LE PEN</WORK_OF_ART>" GOING UP ABOVE AMERICAN <ORG>FLAG</ORG>!'
b'HELP BUILD AND PROTECT'
b'<ORG>BAHAHA</ORG> <SR>/R/PLACE</SR> "BILL <PERSON>CLINTON</PERSON> IS A <ORG>RAPIST</ORG>" COMING TOGETHER, JUST BELOW LINK, LEFT SIDE'
b'COME HELP <GPE>US</GPE> PEDES'
b"<SR>r/place</SR> doesn't want us there."
b'TOO BAD!'
b'GO SHOW THEM ALL OUR HIGH ENERGY!'
b"Obongo: I find <ORG>Trump's</ORG> ties to <GPE>Russia</GPE> troubling."
b'Guys run this script to automatically place pixels to defend the little <PERSON>Donald</PERSON> on <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'The eu flag'
b'REMINDER: Reddit lies about T_D viewership!'
b'<SR>r/place</SR> "has" 8X the active users than T_D right now.'
b'(<CARDINAL>407</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>839</CARDINAL>) <ORG>EU</ORG> flag is falling in <SR>r/place</SR>!'
b'finish it off!'
b'Help build the wall on the southern border of the <GPE>US</GPE> flag'
b'Title'
b'Was checking out <SR>r/Place</SR> when I noticed something strange'
b'I know its a waste of time but you might wanna get to the south of your flag'
b"\xf0\x9f\x9a\xa8\xf0\x9f\x9a\xa8<EVENT>New Plan</EVENT> \xf0\x9f\x9a\xa8\xf0\x9f\x9a\xa8 Let's not attack the top left of <SR>r/place</SR>."
b'Rebuild the <NORP>American</NORP> flag in the middle and then we can build a brick wall around it!!'
b'!'
b'<GPE>Boston</GPE> antifa just went into full ISIS mode'
b'Any way we can get some guys together to write "<WORK_OF_ART>Trump</WORK_OF_ART>" in the place subreddit?'
b'Pedophile is the new protected class.'
b"During <NORP>Infowars</NORP> broadcast on ex-navy SEAL <PERSON>Craig Sawyer</PERSON>'s new operation to expose pedos/save kids from torture (Vets4ChildRescue.org) - YOU CARING crowdsourcing site SHUT HIS ACCOUNT <PERSON>DOWN</PERSON>, GoFundMe froze his account."
b'Brothers!'
b'We need a large pepe in <SR>r/place</SR>.'
b'They need kek!'
b'NEVER FORGET!'
b"Don't fall victim to Spezcaust-Denialist propaganda!"
b"<CARDINAL>Over 5.6 million</CARDINAL> deplorables have been erased from history by <ORG>Reddit</ORG>'s despotic admins"
b"TFW you remember when <SR>/r/The_Donald</SR> completely BTFO of the <ORG>BernieBots</ORG> during <EVENT>the Great Meme War</EVENT> <DATE>last April Fool's Day</DATE>."
b'THE <ORG>FLAG</ORG> IS UNDER FIRE STOP IT BEFORE IT GETS WORSE!!!'
b'!'
b'FullCommunism VANDALIZED an <NORP>American</NORP> flag on <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b"\xf0\x9f\x9a\xa7<ORG>ANTI</ORG>-<ORG>ANTIFA</ORG>\xf0\x9f\x9a\xa7: <ORG>ANTIFA</ORG> Terrorists and <ORG>Their Communist Allies</ORG> have their own little corner on <SR>/r/Place</SR>, let's change that."
b'So, the <ORG>ANTIFA</ORG> terrorists have decided to take their little corner on <SR>/r/Place</SR> and they put their little flag, a Hammer and Sickle (<ORG>SAD</ORG>), and their saying of "<WORK_OF_ART>Bash The Fash</WORK_OF_ART>" (Ironic considering they are more fascist than we\'ll ever be)\n\nLet\'s change that, let\'s teach these terrorists a lesson.'
b'Go in, and get rid of that.'
b"It's simple."
b"We can put <GPE>MAGA</GPE> in if you want, but that comes later, the important part is making sure these criminals can't keep their victory."
b'Link (And the coordinates that they have it at): https://www.reddit.com<SR>/r/place</SR>#x=14&amp;y=474\n\nHave fun, fellow <GPE>Centipedes</GPE>'
b"That face when you realize the reason the shitposts were lacking lately is because pede's were distracted by the cuck cannibal admin's <SR>r/place</SR>."
b'Look what I did'
b'<CARDINAL>10</CARDINAL> FEET HIGHER!!!'
b'\xf0\x9f\x91\xb7\xf0\x9f\x91\xb7\xf0\x9f\x91\xb7 <PERSON>Build</PERSON> a wall around <GPE>Mexico</GPE> on <ORG>Reddit Place</ORG> (x: <CARDINAL>222</CARDINAL>, y: <CARDINAL>333</CARDINAL>) \xf0\x9f\x9a\xa7 \xf0\x9f\x87\xb2\xf0\x9f\x87\xbd'
b'The <ORG>LGBT</ORG> rainbow going over the <NORP>palestinian</NORP> flag is an interesting touch'
b"<ORG>Reddit</ORG>'s new <DATE>April</DATE> Fools page is up."
b'You collectively draw a picture one pixel at a time.'
b'It would be a shame if our <CARDINAL>6 million</CARDINAL> subs wrote the word TRUMP across it.'
b"Let's put red <ORG>Swastikas</ORG> in the middle of of <ORG>EU</ORG> flags."
b'So tired of these whack job professors!'
b'<ORG>GEMRANY</ORG> DEFACED <ORG>THE AMERICAN FLAG</ORG>!!!'
b'EVERYBODY GO PUT A RED WHITE AND BLUE "WW2" ON <ORG>THE GERMAN FLAG</ORG>'
b'Guys, how about we convert this flag to a <ORG>Guacamole</ORG> themed flag?'
b'Save our flag at <SR>/r/place</SR> now'
b'PJW on twitter: "No major monuments in <LOC>Europe</LOC> lit up <TIME>tonight</TIME>.'
b'Are victims of terror less important if they\'re <NORP>Russian</NORP>?"'
b'<ORG>The Washington Post</ORG> took notice, see the Politics section!!'
b'!'
b'Every other country has their flag.'
b'Help me build this in the purple corner!'
b'I made a pretty over at <SR>r/place</SR>.'
b'Hope they like it!'
b'<SR>/r/Place</SR> thread.'
b'The <NORP>Mexicans</NORP> keep trying to destroy our <NORP>British</NORP> flag.'
b'Come help us build a wall and keep them out.'
b'Spotted in <SR>r/place</SR>.'
b'You know what to do.'
b'ADMINS have <PERSON>DEFACED</PERSON> the <PERSON>SHADILAY</PERSON> on <SR>/r/place</SR>!'
b'<ORG>SHAME</ORG>!'
b'[<TIME>9:11:52 PM Eastern](https://abra.me</TIME>/place-snaps/04-01%2001%3a11%3a52.png)\n\n[<TIME>9:11:57 PM</TIME> Eastern](https://abra.me/place-snaps/04-01%2001%3a11%3a57.png)\n\n[<TIME>9:12:02 PM Eastern](https://abra.me</TIME>/place-snaps/04-01%2001%3a12%3a02.png)\n\nNear the middle, to the upper right of <NORP>Helix</NORP>.'
b'Note the broadbrushed removal of the entire <ORDINAL>first</ORDINAL> part of Shadilay in <TIME>just 10 seconds</TIME>.'
b"On [<SR>/r/place</SR>](http://np.reddit.com<SR>/r/place</SR>) the corresponding pixels are now blank... when you click on them you don't see a username... this means this was the work of an admin's blanking tool."
b'We must rebuild the Shadilay with more IMPRESSIVE LENGTH than before!'
b"(Also I'd like a coat, have lurked for a while)"
b'I can only imagine the events that must have led up to this conclusion.'
b'AntiFa are <ORG>LITERAL LARPers</ORG>.'
b'<DATE>Today</DATE> we stand with our <NORP>Russian</NORP> brothers and sisters.'
b'<PERSON>Je Suis</PERSON> <GPE>Russia</GPE> \xf0\x9f\x87\xb7\xf0\x9f\x87\xba'
b'Lets replace the flag of <GPE>Sweden</GPE> on <SR>/r/place</SR> with the flag of <GPE>Somalia</GPE>!'
b'!'
b'<SR>r/place</SR> Rules: Only accounts created before <DATE>31-03-2017</DATE> may place tiles'
b'We leaked into <SR>/r/Place</SR> (INFOWARS.COM)'
b'T_D needs some representation on the new <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'CONVICTION.'
b'Meet <PERSON>Lil Wayne</PERSON>.'
b'The <ORG>Media</ORG> TWICE Tried to Bully Him into <PERSON>Supporting Black</PERSON> Lives <PERSON>Matter</PERSON>.'
b'However, he Knew his <FAC>Job</FAC> was to <ORG>Rap</ORG>, Not "Be a Damn <NORP>Politician</NORP>."'
b'<SR>/r/Place</SR> getting work done'
b'Calling all reinforcements!'
b'Our glorious flag is under attack.'
b'<NORP>Shia</NORP> Lacucks flag just got taken down after <TIME>25 hours</TIME> in liverpool.'
b'Did you catch that?'
b"<TIME>25 HOURS</TIME>, that's all it took."
b'It just proves we have pedes in the <GPE>UK</GPE> as well.'
b'Cheers mates.'
b'Can we get this pepe on <SR>/r/Place</SR>?'
b'We can do it!'
b'YOU HELPED BUILD THE <ORG>FLAG</ORG>, <ORG>NOW</ORG> HELP REPAIR AND DEFEND IT'
b"IT'S NOT BIG ENOUGH GET ON OUR FLAG DISCORD AND HELP MANIFEST DESTINY ALL OVER <PERSON>PLACE</PERSON> https://discord.gg/zvQ97"
b'Keep Going Pedes!!!'
b'!'
b'<ORG>Buzzfeed</ORG> hacked by 4Chan!'
b"<ORG>Reddit</ORG>'s <SR>r/Place</SR> openly advocates for violence."
b'Imagine if this said "Bash the Commie" or "Bash the <NORP>Muslim</NORP>" instead.'
b'To SJWs anyone not with them is a fascist.'
b'<SR>r/Place</SR> is "Fake Shitposting."'
b'The real action is on <SR>r/The_Donald</SR>.'
b'MEET <PRODUCT>THE MAN</PRODUCT> HOLDING YOUTUBE HOSTAGE: DOUCHEBAG BLACKMAILING YOUTUBERS BY CUTTING OFF THEIR ADS SO HE GETS PROTECTION MONEY.'
b'LEFTIST MAFIA IS <ORG>REAL</ORG>.'
b"That face when you realize the reason the shitposts were lacking lately is because pede's were distracted by the cuck cannibal admin's <SR>r/place</SR>."
b"We <ORG>NEED</ORG> an <NORP>American</NORP> flag in <GPE>Place</GPE> there's commies and eurocucks but <ORG>no Old Glory</ORG>?!"
b'Go to <SR>r/Americanflaginplace</SR> to help with the efforts'
b'This is our flag right now on <SR>r/place</SR>.'
b'Will our flag make it through the night?'
b'Will you do your part pede?'
b'Why the <ORG>FUCK</ORG> is this still here??'
b'A grand total of <CARDINAL>50</CARDINAL> users from here can dismantle this symbol attributed to <CARDINAL>20 million</CARDINAL> deaths'
b'<GPE>Kekistan</GPE> needs our help!'
b'Go to place to defend our nation!'
b'Can someone finish the Pepe on this pixel generator?'
b'NEED HELP FROM THE PEDES'
b"FUCK <SR>/R/PLACE</SR>, it's a distraction for kids and communists - we already control the most powerful PLACE on <LOC>EARTH</LOC>."
b"We're painting a <ORG>PEPE</ORG> on <SR>/r/place</SR>!"
b'Come help us!'
b'<ORG>KEK</ORG> WILLS IT!'
b'HELP <GPE>US</GPE> <ORG>BUILD A</ORG> WALL ON OUR SOUTHERN BORDER AT <SR>R/PLACE</SR>'
b"That's a nice flag on <SR>/r/place</SR>, would be a same if someone BUILT A WALL"
b'Just a happy little Jeb!'
b'I think we have ourselves a spot.'
b'Do work Pedes!'
b"Would be a shame if <SR>r/Sweden's</SR> flag became a <NORP>Trump</NORP> flag, wouldn't it?"
b'\xf0\x9f\x94\xa5 \xf0\x9f\x94\xa5 SUPER SPICY BEN GARRISON: DISHONEST BEARACK \xf0\x9f\x94\xa5 \xf0\x9f\x94\xa5'
b'<NORP>Communists</NORP> and <ORG>Antifa</ORG> are trying to stake out there space on <SR>r/place</SR> (on the left, of course).'
b"There's a battle to replace <ORG>CCCP</ORG> with <ORG>CUCK</ORG>--ARE YOU DOING YOUR PART, PEDES?"
b'?'
b'https://www.reddit.com<SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'Mods can we please get a sticky to coordinate an effort on <SR>r/place</SR>?'
b'There are <CARDINAL>6 million</CARDINAL> of us, if we work together we can accomplish greatness.'
b"<SR>r/MURICA</SR> and <ORG>AFIP</ORG> are on board, let's get this badass eagle of patriotism on our flag!"
b'They destroyed <SR>r/THE_DONALD</SR> from <SR>/r/Place</SR>.'
b'Time to retaliate by destroying their precious hammer and sickle, located on the far left'
b'Not all heroes wear capes.'
b"While people on the right can deduce and pinpoint the location of a secret flag anywhere on earth, people on the left can't figure out which bathroom to use."
b'The commies are drawing a hammer and sickle on <SR>r/place</SR>, help deface it!'
b'https://www.reddit.com/place\n\ncoordinates: 108,22 (top left corner)'
b'<GPE>China</GPE> bans \xe2\x80\x98<ORG>abnormal\xe2\x80\x99 beards</ORG> &amp; veils to curb extremism in <NORP>Muslim</NORP> region.'
b'~ I think we should sponsor a <GPE>PussyHat</GPE>/<ORG>ANTIFA</ORG> protest and see how many volunteers we get.'
b'Help Us Fight AnComs'
b'I know you folk have your own projects and defenses to hold.'
b'But we are all best when we work in cohesion to fight the <ORG>AnComs</ORG>.'
b'Help us defend Snek!'
b'Defend yourselves!'
b'Why does this video only have <CARDINAL>75,000</CARDINAL> Views??'
b"Rep. <PERSON>Roskam Unveils</PERSON> <ORG>the Select Committee's</ORG> #<MONEY>BenghaziReport</MONEY>"
b"Why isn't our God Emperor taking up all of <ORG>Reddit Place?&gt</ORG>;"
b'The true definition of mental illness'
b'Pedes!'
b'Trolls, shills and cucks have attacked Old Glory!'
b'Go to place and defend her!'
b'(<CARDINAL>500,500</CARDINAL>)'
b"<PERSON>Ahn Cheol-soo</PERSON> is a <ORDINAL>third</ORDINAL> party candidate for <GPE>South Korea's</GPE> presidential election in <DATE>May.</DATE>"
b"He went from <PERCENT>8%</PERCENT> support in <DATE>March</DATE> in a <CARDINAL>five</CARDINAL>-person race to beating the 'media darling' liberal candidate <PERSON>Moon</PERSON> in a <CARDINAL>two</CARDINAL>-person race <DATE>today</DATE>."
b"Ahn went to the same college as <ORG>TRUMP</ORG> and he's a self-made billionaire!!!"
b'!'
b'Call to arms!'
b'Make a Pepe on <SR>R/Place</SR>'
b'We need to impose our presence on <SR>R/Place</SR> by making a pepe.'
b'We can even coordinate with <SR>R/4chan</SR> for help.'
b'I say we make it on the rainbow at (<CARDINAL>572</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>422</CARDINAL>)'
b'Rally the Troops!'
b"We're bringing <GPE>MAGA</GPE> to <SR>/r/place</SR> - and we need your help!"
b'(Automated Script inside)'
b'CALLING ALL CENTIPEDES!-No More Censorship'
b'OUR FLAG STANDS TALL CENTIPEDES'
b'<SR>r/place</SR> is disgraceful'
b"Attack and Defense of the <NORP>American</NORP> flag <TIME>last night</TIME>: They can't put us down, freedom triumphs!"
b'Get over to <SR>R/place</SR>'
b'Member when those slow and steady guys at /Testudinidae captured the flag?'
b'This would be a great replacement for the communist flag at (<CARDINAL>0,410</CARDINAL>)'
b'Fellow Patriots, your help is needed over in <SR>r/place</SR>.'
b'Defend Your Flag!'
b'THE <ORDINAL>45th</ORDINAL>: <GPE>Melania</GPE> and I are honored to light up <FAC>the White House</FAC> <TIME>this evening</TIME>, for <CARDINAL>\xe2\x80\xac</CARDINAL> \xe2\x80\xaa#WorldAutismAwarenessDay.'
b'You know Reddit is Cucked when the <NORP>American</NORP> flag is taking more of a beating on <SR>/r/place</SR> than the <NORP>Turkish</NORP> flag.'
b'Just go check it out.'
b"The <NORP>Turkish</NORP> flag is where we're trying to have <ORG>Trump</ORG>."
b"<ORG>SJW</ORG>'s hate it here so much that they want to stay and bring more people here"
b'Take down the <ORG>EU</ORG> flag at (<CARDINAL>423</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>843</CARDINAL>) in <SR>r/place</SR>.'
b'Calling all <NORP>Russian</NORP> trolls, professional shitposters, and <NORP>Americans</NORP>'
b"<GPE>Germany</GPE>'s flag is currently the biggest in <SR>r/place</SR>."
b'This is an abomination that cannot continue.'
b'Make America Great Again!'
b'Fix shadilay in <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'liberals are destorying it with the rainbow thing'
b'FullCommunism and other commie subs are plastering a pro-<GPE>Soviet Union</GPE> mural onto <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'Help Protect Pepe on <SR>r/Place</SR>!'
b'Top Right Corner (<CARDINAL>958</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>94</CARDINAL>)'
b'WE NEED AN <ORG>AMERICAN FLAG ON</ORG> <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'Pedes, we need to remind reddit which country is the best!'
b'Start at (<CARDINAL>32</CARDINAL>, <DATE>86</DATE>)'
b'REINFORCEMENTS NEEDED!!'
b'!'
b"Reddit mobile glitched, &amp; I didn't have to wait between painting squares in <SR>r/place</SR>..."
b"There's no trump on <SR>/r/place</SR> right now"
b'REINFORCEMENTS NEEDED!'
b'We at <SR>r/AFIP</SR> noticed that of all the flags on the <SR>r/place</SR> canvas, the <CARDINAL>one</CARDINAL> lacking was our glorious <NORP>American</NORP> Flag.'
b'We are now trying to fix this by building a massive flag.'
b'We are being attacked on all fronts by The <PERSON>Void</PERSON> and <ORG>EU</ORG> freedom hating cucks.'
b'Click the link to help!'
b'We must destroy <ORG>the EU Flag</ORG> on <SR>r/place</SR> !'
b'<SR>/r/place</SR> is woke'
b'We will no longer surrender our subreddit - nor its centipedes - to the false song of <SR>/r/place</SR>!'
b'Out out out'
b'Help fight commies on <SR>r/place</SR>!'
b'THIS IS NOT A DRILL: REDDIT ADMINS ARE NOW HIDING THE LIES!!!!!!!!'
b'REDDIT CAUGHT LYING!!!'
b'<ORG>REDDIT</ORG> NOW HIDING THE REAL SUBSCRIPTION COUNT!!!'
b'BOYCOTT REDDIT NOOOOOOW'
b'O<SR>R/WA</SR> Patriots We Out Here!!'
b'!'
b'Tell me what to write pedes'
b'<DATE>Tomorrow</DATE> at <DATE>Friday</DATE> Prayer, <FAC>Mosques</FAC> across <GPE>America</GPE> will fly this flag to show that <NORP>Muslims</NORP> love gay people and respect their rights.'
b'Can we do something similar to <SR>r/place</SR> to <ORG>PROVE</ORG> how many current active users there are?'
b'We know the subscriber count is screwed off, might could get an idea of current active users there are too'
b'<ORG>Old Glory</ORG> has fallen in <SR>r/place</SR>!'
b'<PERSON>Uncle Sam</PERSON> needs you!'
b"C'mon pedes lets show em we're <CARDINAL>6 MILLION</CARDINAL> STRONG!!!"
b'Lets put this up at (<CARDINAL>480,480</CARDINAL>)'
b'<SR>R/place</SR> gave me like <QUANTITY>a hundred</QUANTITY> blocks in a row, so now it says fuck M, need some help spelling the <GPE>Exico</GPE>'
b'I was gonna put a <NORP>Russian</NORP> flag filter over my profile pic, but pretty sure <ORG>US Media</ORG> would label that collusion with <PERSON>Putin</PERSON>.'
b'<ORG>#MAKE_SWEDEN_BROWN_AGAIN</ORG> <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'\xe2\x80\x9cShocked\xe2\x80\x9d at the values, or lack thereof, exhibited by millennials, a religious leader suggests <NORP>Christians</NORP> need mass exodus from public schools'
b'Am I doing this right?'
b"The best thing I've ever seen."
b'disappointed with the lack of america on <SR>r/place</SR> <DATE>today</DATE>...'
b'Today I witnessed brain energy needlessly expended on guacamole, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>M subscribers, and retired memes <SR>r/place</SR>?'
b'I know we are all abuzz about the sub count thing but there is an urgent matter at hand'
b'The Pepe on <SR>r/place</SR> has been desecrated and needs rebuilt.'
b'He is currently residing on the left side in the middle, just follows the REEES.'
b"We need to make a stand for <ORG>Pepe</ORG>'s rights!"
b"Let's take the <ORG>EU</ORG> flag down from <GPE>Place</GPE>!"
b'<GPE>Spaz</GPE> is a <NORP>Nazi</NORP> confirmed, disappearing <CARDINAL>6 million</CARDINAL> people of the same group.'
b'Someone is busy at work on <DATE>this Monday</DATE>!'
b'Remember this is <PERSON>Steve Huffman</PERSON>.'
b'He is the one responsible for all the <ORG>Reddit</ORG> fu\xf0\x9f\x91\x8e<GPE>Kery</GPE> we are experiences.'
b'I made another pixel art for <SR>/r/Place</SR>!'
b'Shall we get working on it?'
b'<ORG>SAD</ORG>!'
b'The <NORP>American</NORP> flag needs help on <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'<PERSON>Colin Kaepernick</PERSON> here.'
b'I was adopted by a white family after my black dad took off.'
b'My family helped me to excel in school and sports and eventually land in the <ORG>NFL</ORG>.'
b'Despite all that I made it a personal campaign to disrespect the <GPE>USA</GPE> in the name of "racial equality".'
b"I'm now washed up and jobless!"
b'<GPE>Sweden</GPE> drew over <NORP>Danish</NORP> flag.'
b"Lets help our <NORP>Danish</NORP> pedes and show these cucks that they can't even conquer an art piece!"
b'<SR>/r/bluecorner</SR> supports <ORG>Blue</ORG> lives matter'
b'[RED-ALERT] <GPE>America</GPE>-haters are attacking our flag in <SR>/r/place</SR> pedes!'
b'We need your help!'
b'<ORG>REDDIT</ORG> ADMINS ARE NOW SHADOW BANNING OUR STICKIED POSTS!'
b'EXCELLENT NEWS!'
b'Breaking News: @SenJohnMcCain announces he plans to vote to confirm <PERSON>Neil Gorsuch</PERSON> to <ORG>SCOTUS</ORG>, becoming first <ORG>Senate</ORG> <NORP>Democrat</NORP> to back nominee.'
b'Help With The Flag!'
b'Get in there pedes!'
b'REINFORCEMENTS NEEDED!'
b'We are <SR>r/AFIP</SR> noticed that of all the flags on the <SR>r/places</SR> canvas, the <CARDINAL>one</CARDINAL> lacking was our glorious <NORP>American</NORP> Flag.'
b'We are now trying to fix this by building a massive flag in the center of the canvas.'
b'We are being attacked on all fronts and need help!'
b'AntiFa finally shows its true colours'
b'This is <ORG>Pepe</ORG>.'
b'<ORG>Pepe Used</ORG> To Be a <ORG>Front-Page Mainstay</ORG>.'
b'But <ORG>Pepe</ORG> is Sad Because He Has Seemingly Fallen Out of <ORG>Favor</ORG> on <SR>/r/the_donald</SR>.'
b"Let's Show This BASED Amphibian Some Love, and Show Him That We Care!"
b"<DATE>Daily</DATE> reminder to the left: You're allied with these <CARDINAL>two</CARDINAL> war criminals against Trump!"
b'The left has become a parody of itself!'
b"We're in the best timeline folks!"
b'tolerant left shoes his true xenophobic colors'
b'LOOK WHAT I JUST GOT IN THE MAIL!!!'
b"Can't wait to bring this to the next Trump rally!"
b'Make America great again'
b'Liberals yelling false flag.'
b'Amazing.'
b'No candle vigils and <ORG>Facebook</ORG> pictures for <GPE>Russia</GPE>?'
b'So did we give up on <SR>r/Place</SR>?'
b"Because they're mocking us over there."
b'<SR>/R/Place</SR> needs your help!'
b'Make it great again!'
b'Your pixel flag is in peril'
b'Look at all those facebook profiles with the <NORP>Russian</NORP> flag overlay on their picture!...'
b'Oh wait...'
b'<ORG>CNN</ORG> literally helping criminals.'
b"<ORG>Reddit</ORG>'s <SR>r/Place</SR> openly advocates for violence."
b"I don't think <ORG>Reddit</ORG>'s advertisers would be happy with this."
b'Imagine if this said "Bash the <NORP>Muslim</NORP>" instead.'
b'Can this pixel <ORG>Pepe</ORG> get some love?'
b"What's everyone up to <DATE>this weekend</DATE>?"
b"I hope it doesn't involve brakes cause the trump train don't stop!"
b'Jeb phenomemeon spreads to <GPE>Poland</GPE>'
b'These shills want to keep <PERSON>Donald</PERSON> off of <SR>/r/Place</SR>.'
b"You know what to do 'Pedes!"
b'Tell whatever cuck is false-flagging /MLPOL/ to knock that shit off.'
b'With our <CARDINAL>6 Million</CARDINAL> strong PEDES lets get Trump on <SR>/r/place</SR>!'
b"There's some sort of glitch on <SR>r/place</SR> that allowed me to place a bunch on tiles at once :D"
b'the whole "place" thing will be censored faster that you can say bill clinton i'
b'WE ARE MAKING <SR>/R/PLACES</SR> GREAT AGAIN!'
b'HELP <GPE>US</GPE> <ORG>BUILD</ORG> AND DEFEND TRUMP!'
b'So you are telling me almost all of reddit believes that the <ORG>WSJ</ORG> reported fake news over <ORG>YouTube</ORG> ads, but when we suggest that the media reports fake news against <NORP>Trump</NORP> we are all <NORP>Russian</NORP> bots?'
b'Do these people need any more evidence as to why no one takes them seriously?'
b"So, I think it's interesting the cucks are putting a gay pride flag on top of the <GPE>US</GPE> flag over 'the_donald' because they think it bothers us"
b"We should let them finish it and write the_Donald in a way that includes the gay pride flag to show that it doesn't."
b'<SR>R/the_donald</SR> is with the gay community not afraid or angered by it.'
b'ATTENTION PEDES!'
b'MEXICANS AND IMMIGRANTS ARE FLOODING IN <SR>R/PLACE</SR>!'
b'HEAD TO <LAW>THE LEFT SIDE OF</LAW> THE <ORG>MAP</ORG>, AND HELP <GPE>US</GPE> <ORG>CONSTRUCT</ORG> THE BORDER WALL!'
b'WE NEED YOU!!'
b'<ORG>CORDINATES</ORG> (<CARDINAL>5,332</CARDINAL>)!'
b'!'
b'It seems <GPE>France</GPE> is need of some <NORP>American</NORP> intervention as <GPE>Germany</GPE> seeks to invade them again (/Place)'
b'<SR>r/place</SR> - pepe up next'
b'<PERSON>Chelsea Clinton</PERSON> wears upside down crosses on her necklace.'
b'Is she part of some satanic cult or something?'
b'I think those place posts are mostly from shills'
b'Question is why are they brigading us with those?'
b'<GPE>Egypt</GPE>\'s President is referring to President <PERSON>Trump</PERSON> as "Your Excellency" in their meeting right now.'
b'God-Emperor confirmed.'
b"If anyone is still interested in <SR>r/place</SR>, at <CARDINAL>420,980</CARDINAL> there's a free internet tab we could put TD at"
b'After making the mistake of viewing <SR>r/worldnews</SR> I stumbled upon this masterpiece of a comment about <PERSON>Flynn</PERSON>.'
b"I can't hold back the cringe"
b'FullCommunism VANDALIZED an <NORP>American</NORP> flag on <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'PEDES!'
b'WE NEED YOU IN <EVENT>THE WAR ROOM</EVENT> RIGHT NOW!'
b"WE HAVE A TRUMP THAT'S <PERCENT>95%</PERCENT> FINISHED IN <SR>R/PLACE</SR> BUT IT'S GETTING GRIEFED *HARD*!"
b'GET IN HERE AND HELP <GPE>US</GPE> FINISH IT!'
b'<SR>r/Denmark</SR> requesting help fighting the <NORP>Islamic</NORP> Caliphate of <GPE>Sweden</GPE>.'
b"<PERSON>Ted Cruz</PERSON> here, by golly if you don't come out in full force and protect <GPE>Dahnold</GPE> on <SR>r/place</SR>, well then you got another thing coming for ya."
b'I tell you what.'
b'St <GPE>Petersburg</GPE> metro explosions kills <CARDINAL>10</CARDINAL>.'
b'Anyone else wagering that this is the doing of the "religion of peace" ?'
b'?'
b'Keep the <NORP>American</NORP> flag safe!'
b'Clean it up and expand it!'
b'<SR>/r/place</SR> is trying to destroy it!'
b'PEDES get to <SR>r/place</SR>!!!'
b'The flag is getting killed!'
b'!'
b'It seems that <ORG>Antifa</ORG> and the commies are trying to set up turf on the place.'
b'I say we turn it into a nice <PERSON>Jeb Bush</PERSON> approved <PERSON>Guac Bowl</PERSON>.'
b'I see the perfect spot for a pepe here, roughly between the <NORP>French</NORP> flag and the <NORP>German</NORP> flag, anyone in?'
b'<ORG>EU</ORG> boss threatens to break up the <GPE>USA</GPE>.'
b'Good luck pal.'
b'I think you need to worry about your own break up.'
b'If we can just get a couple of people together and destroy the facist flag!'
b'!'
b'<GPE>MAGA</GPE> on <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'We need your help against the commies at <SR>r/place</SR>'
b'Bit by bit, <NORP>Trump</NORP> methodically undoing <PERSON>Obama</PERSON> policies'
b"<ORG>CNN</ORG>: <PERSON>Putin</PERSON> stages false flag terrorist attack to deflect attention from <ORG>Trump's</ORG> corrupt ties to the <ORG>Kremlin</ORG>"
b'Are we really going to let this travesty stand?'
b'Sad.'
b"(<SR>/r/place</SR>) Please don't greif our <NORP>Swedish</NORP> flag."
b"I'm definitely pro-trump <GPE>Sweden</GPE> is becoming <GPE>Swedenistan</GPE>, but greifing is unnecessary!"
b'- Love, <GPE>Sweden</GPE>'
b'<SR>/r/Place</SR> Soldiers'
b'We took some heavy hits from the cucks, but we can still do it, keep strong centipedes!'
b"VENEZUELA: I can't give you $<MONEY>15/hour</MONEY> to flip hamburgers at <ORG>McDonalds</ORG>."
b'However, I am here to single-handedly SAVE YOUR ECONOMY with <ORG>the RAREST of INTERGALACTIC PEPES</ORG>!'
b'Put this Pepe in your retirement portfolio and <ORG>NEVER</ORG> know poverty again!'
b'<ORG>KEK</ORG> BE UPON YOU, <GPE>VENEZUELA</GPE>!'
b'\xf0\x9f\x87\xbb<GPE>\xf0\x9f\x87\xaa</GPE>\xf0\x9f\x87\xbb<GPE>\xf0\x9f\x87\xaa</GPE>\xf0\x9f\x87\xbb<GPE>\xf0\x9f\x87\xaa</GPE>'
b'Concerning <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b"Why haven't we spread our message to the great people of the place?"
b'I think we pedes can commandeer a spot, in order to write something showing we are reddit!'
b'The donald image and script for <SR>/r/place</SR>'
b'https://i.redd.it/wd0zzr2a71py.png\n\nTo assist in forming our fearless leaders image on <SR>/r/place</SR>, perform the following steps.'
b'<PERSON>Install Greasemonkey</PERSON> for firefox: https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/greasemonkey/\n\nInstall <ORG>Placebot</ORG> for greasemonkey: https://github.com/grind086/PlaceBot/raw/maste<SR>r/dist/placebot</SR>.user.js\n\nOpen up the <ORG>Java</ORG> console while you have <SR>/r/place</SR> open: (<ORG>Ctrl-Shift-K</ORG>)\n\n<GPE>Paste</GPE> the following code into the console.'
b'Every time you refresh the page, it will start checking and repairing from the top down.'
b"Go get 'em 'pedes!"
b'placeBot.tiles = [\n[<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>133</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 134, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, 134, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>134</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 135, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>135</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>136</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>137</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>138</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 139, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>139</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 140, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, 140, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, 140, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>140</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>141</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 142, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>6</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>142</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>143</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 144, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, 144, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>144</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>1</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>145</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 146, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>146</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>147</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>148</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>149</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 150, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>150</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>5</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>151</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <DATE>152</DATE>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>152</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>0</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>153</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, 153, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>2</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>154</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>155</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>8</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>156</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 157, 11], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [435, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>13</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>157</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 158, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>158</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>159</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 160, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>160</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 161, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>161</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, 162, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>435</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <DATE>162</DATE>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>13</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>162</CARDINAL>, <DATE>11</DATE>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>3</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>163</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>428</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>429</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>430</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>431</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>432</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>433</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>434</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [435, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>436</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>437</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>438</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>439</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>440</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>441</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>442</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>443</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>444</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>445</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>], [<CARDINAL>446</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>164</CARDINAL>, <CARDINAL>11</CARDINAL>],\n    ];\nplaceBot.tileSelector = PlaceBot.selector.<GPE>TopDown</GPE>;\nplaceBot.save();'
b'I made another pixel art for the amazing President <PERSON>Trump</PERSON>!'
b'OUR GLORIOUS <ORG>FLAG</ORG> <GPE>NEEDS</GPE> YOUR HELP!!!'
b'!'
b"LET'S HELP <SR>/R/</SR><ORG>MURICA</ORG> MAKE THE <ORG>FLAG</ORG> ON <SR>/R/PLACE</SR> GREAT AGAIN!"
b'Help Make <SR>R/Place</SR> Great Again'
b'<CARDINAL>One</CARDINAL> of the things on <SR>r/Place</SR>.'
b"They said that The_Donald must be very disorganized if they don't even have their own corner in <SR>r/place</SR> , and they said don't taunt us , or you'll see a giant <GPE>MAGA</GPE> sign in the corner."
b'Lets show them that we  are organized , and not to taunt us.'
b"Let's build that <GPE>MAGA</GPE> sign!"
b'<SR>/R/</SR><ORG>MURICA</ORG> has a chrome script to defend our flag, do your part pedes!'
